Guide to the Harold J. Gibson Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Harold J. Gibson papers
circa 1910s-2002
1930-1980
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5866
5866-001
Gibson, Harold J.,$d1913-1984
15.17 cubic feet (19 boxes)
Materials relating to Harold Gibson's life and his career as an officer in the International Association of Machinists, District 751
Harold J. Gibson was an important leader in the history of the International Association of Machinists, and an influential figure in labor politics, both in the Pacific Northwest and nationally. Born in Idaho in 1913, he moved to Washington State as a child, eventually graduating from Lake Washington High School in Kirkland, WA in 1931. After graduation, Gibson joined the Army for a time before beginning work at Boeing in 1936. In 1941, he was elected a Business Representative of his local District Lodge 751, and in 1943, a short two years later, he was elected District President, a position he would hold for the next 13 years. During World War II, Gibson reenlisted, taking a leave of absence from his post to serve as a sergeant in Patton’s Third Army. In his tenure after the war, he led a successful strike in 1948, ended government freezes on aircraft workers’ wages, helped the district win its first all-inclusive health and welfare plan, and significantly increased union membership. In 1956, Gibson was elected to nationwide office as a General Vice President of the International Association of Machinists, and held the position through the mid-1960s. Gibson was influential not only as a labor leader, but as a political figure as well. He was well connected with longtime state Senators Warren Magnuson and Henry "Scoop" Jackson, Governor Al Rosellini, and Bill Boeing. He was an active participant in the Democratic Party, and sat on many committees and commissions. Harold Gibson passed away in 1984 at the age of 71.
Materials relating to Harold Gibson's life and his career as an officer in the International Association of Machinists, District 751.
Open to all users.
International Association of Machinists.$bAeronautical Industrial District Lodge 751; Gibson, Harold J.,$d1913-1984$vArchives; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers$vConstitution; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers$vCongresses; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers.$bDistrict 751; Boeing Aircraft Company$xEmployees.; Washington State Federation of Labor$vCongresses.; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Labor unions$zWashington (State); Labor movement$zWashington (State); Labor$zWashington (State); Labor union members$zWashington (State); Collective bargaining$zWashington (State); Machinists$xLabor unions$zWashington (State); Aviation mechanics (Persons)$xLabor unions$zWashington (State); Constitutions; Conference materials; Personal correspondence; Business correspondence; Scrapbooks; Ephemera; Photographs; Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor Unions; Labor History
- COLLECTION OF BOOKS AND PUBLISHED WORKS, 1944-1990; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 1/1-2/18)
  - Instructions to Committeemen Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge No. 751, c. 1945 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - In Memoriam: Franklin Delano Roosevelt- from Warren G. Magnuson, 1946 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement- Boeing and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers 1992 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement- Boeing and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers 1983 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Labor Relations Agreement between Boeing Aircraft Company and International Association of Machinists and Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge No. 751, 1944 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between Boeing Airplane Company and Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge No. 751, and Banana River Lodge 2061, and the International Association of Machinists 1958 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1966 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1969 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1981 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1977 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1986 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1980 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1977 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1974 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1989 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - 1957 Legislative Manual (Box-folder 1/16)
  - 1965 Legislative Manual (Box-folder 1/17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1970 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - Constitution and Statutes- Order of Elks 1952-1953 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1954 (Box-folder 1/20)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers-Helen Gibson, 1965 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1971 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1967 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists, 1963 (Box-folder 1/24)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists, 1960 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge No. 751 International Association of Machinists, 1956 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1966 (Box-folder 1/28)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge No. 751 International Association of Machinists, 1955 (Box-folder 1/29)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge No. 751 International Association of Machinists - Jerry Hall, 1954 (Box-folder 1/30)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge No. 751 International Association of Machinists, 1953 (Box-folder 1/31)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between The Boeing Company and Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge No. 751 International Association of Machinists, 1951 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1973 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Agreement between the Boeing Airplane Company, Wichita Division and the International Association of Machinists District Lodge No. 70- Stockinger, 1956 (Box-folder 1/34)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between the Boeing Company, Seattle and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers- Helen Gibson, 1968 (Box-folder 1/35)
  - Directory Democratic National Convention Chicago 1956- Sketch by Daryl Brothman (Delegate from Tacoma) (Box-folder 1/36)
  - Chicago Tourist Brochure, 1956 (Box-folder 1/37)
  - The Harriman Digest - Averill Harriman Campaign Brochure, c. 1956 (Box-folder 1/38)
  - A Decade of Progress - Containing contracts 1950-1960 (Box-folder 1/39)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1977 (Box-folder 1/40)
  - 1959 Legislative Manual (Box-folder 1/41)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1981 (Box-folder 1/42)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution, 1970 (Box-folder 1/43)
  - The Fighting Machinists: A Century of Struggle by Robert G Rodden, post 1977 (Box-folder 1/44)
  - We Build Them Right: Collective Bargaining Agreement Between the Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers AFL/CIO 1995 (Box-folder 1/45)
  - Working Together into the Millennium: Collective Bargaining Agreement 1999 Between the Boeing Company and the International Association of Machinist and Aerospace Workers AFL-CIO (Box-folder 1/46)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement 2002 Between International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers AFL-CIO and the Boeing Company (Box-folder 1/47)
  - The Union Member Speaks- Book based on survey done by Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations at the University of Illinois on member's opinions on IAM District 9's policies, 1955 (Box-folder 1/48)
  - Proceedings of Third International Conference Aircraft and Guided Missile Lodges, 1954 (Box-folder 1/49)
  - Proceedings Fourth International Aircraft and Guided Missile Conference, 1955 (Box-folder 1/50)
  - Recommendations Fifth International Aircraft and Guided Missile Conference, 1956 (Box-folder 1/51)
  - Proceedings of the 29th International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Grand Lodge Convention, 1976 (Box-folder 1/52)
  - IAM Officer's' Guide, 1967 (Box-folder 1/53)
  - District Lodge 751 Booklet: Your Security Under: Health and Welfare Plan, Retirement Plan, Workmen's Compensation, Unemployment Compensation, Old Age and Survivors Insurance, 1956 (Box-folder 1/54)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Pension Plans for Grand Lodge Officers, Representatives and Employees, 1969 (Box-folder 1/55)
  - 1st Constitutional Convention Proceedings- AFL-CIO, 1955 (Box-folder 1/56)
  - Washington State Federation of Labor Proceedings of the 51st Annual Convention, 1953 (Box-folder 1/57)
  - Washington State Federation of Labor Proceedings of the 52st Annual Convention, 1954 (Box-folder 1/58)
  - Washington State Federation of Labor Proceedings of the 53st Annual Convention, 1955 (Box-folder 1/59)
  - Washington State Federation of Labor Proceedings of the 54st Annual Convention, 1956 (Box-folder 1/60)
  - Stewards Manual, 1985 (Box-folder 1/61)
  - No Retreat from Tomorrow - Gift from President Johnson, 1967 (Box-folder 1/62)
  - Olympia 1936- Olympic Souvenir Book, note inside: points for inspection 14 sept 1945 company B 83rd Armored Reconnaissance Battalion APO 253 US Army (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Signed 1965 International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Constitution (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Deutschland Erwacht (1933)- Book about Nazi Germany in German, Correspondence with Admiral Richard E. Byrd, 1943 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Pacific Northwest Goes to War- State of Washington, 1944 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Proceedings of International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Convention, Cincinnati, OH, 1980 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Proceedings of International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Convention, Los Angeles, CA, 1972 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Proceedings of International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Convention, Hollywood, FL, 1976 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Official Circulars, 1944-1968 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Boeing Airplane Company Telephone Directory, 1957 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Proceedings of International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Convention, Chicago, IL, 1968 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Ferrovia Del Gottardo E I Tre Laghi: Sent from Sgt Gibson to Mrs. Harold J Gibson, 1945 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Pacific Northwest Goes to War: Sent from Associated Editors to Harold Gibson, 1944 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Absenteeism in Seattle War Plants- Henry T. Buechel- Sponsored by Seattle Civilian War Commission and College of Economics and Business, 1943 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Officers' Report - Grand Lodge International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1972 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Roster of the International Association of Machinists and Ladies Auxiliary, IAM, 1962 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - Speaker of the House: The Political Career and Times of John L. O'Brien by Daniel Jack Chasan- Signed, 1990 (Box-folder 2/16)
  - Blood in the Water: A History of District Lodge 751 of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers by John McCann, 1989 (Box-folder 2/17)
  - Report of the Aerospace Dispute, 1962 (Box-folder 2/18)
- PERSONAL RECORD BOOKS, 1943-1971; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 3/1-3/15)
  - Cash Ledger, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Cash Ledger, 1953-1957 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Cash Ledger, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Cash Ledger, c.1948 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Account Ledger, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Day Book, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Datebook 1943, used through March (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Desk Diary- Daily schedule log, 1959 (Box-folder 3/8)
  - Desk Diary- Daily schedule log, 1958 (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Desk Diary- Daily schedule log- Incomplete, 1958 (Box-folder 3/10)
  - Desk Diary- Daily Schedule Log, 1960 (Box-folder 3/11)
  - Desk Diary- Daily Schedule Log, 1961 (Box-folder 3/12)
  - Desk Diary- Daily Schedule Log, 1962 (Box-folder 3/13)
  - Desk Diary- Daily Schedule Log, 1963 (Box-folder 3/14)
  - Desk Diary- Daily Schedule Log, 1964 (Box-folder 3/15)
- DOCUMENTS RELATED TO THE ASSOCIATION OF MACHINISTS AND AEROSPACE WORKERS, DEMOCRATIC PARTY POLITICS, AND PERSONAL LIFE, c. 1910s-2012; SERIES 3 (Box-folder 3/17-8/16)
  - Scrapbook Box (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Box: 1/5 Aerospace Industrial District Lodge 751 Absence Authorization Slips- Helen Gibson, 1973-1989 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Box: 2/5 Delegate's Credential- 23rd Convention Grand Lodge of International Association of Machinists, Kansas City, MO, 1952 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Box: 3/5 Elect Harold J. Gibson, General Vice President- Campaign Fliers, 1957 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Box: 4/5 Paycheck Receipts/Stubs Helen Gibson, Inc. 1985 Switch to Boeing Employee Credit Union, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Box: 5/5 District Lodge 751- Dues Book 1983-1984 (Box-folder 3/17)
  - Joe Addison (Plaintiff) vs. Grand Lodge of the I.A.M., 1962 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Correspondence- Invitations as General Vice President, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Shareowner Information- Federated American Insurance Company, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Correspondence- Gift Fund, Northwest Territory, 1958-1966 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Correspondence- A.J. Hayes, International President, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Personal Correspondence/Veterans Brochures, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Monte-Copter Shareholder Information, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 4/9)
  - Public Service Award for Service on the United Jobs Corps Committee, Biographical Information, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 4/10)
  - General and Political Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/11)
  - Life Insurance, Retirement Benefits Information, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 4/12)
  - District Lodge #751 Grand Lodge Auditor's Report 1954-1957 and Related Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box-folder 4/13)
  - Income Tax Records-1/3: Airplane Tickets, Hotel Tickets, Expenses for Travel, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 4/14)
  - Income Tax Records- 2/3 Gas, Car, Parking Receipts, 1957 (Box-folder 4/15)
  - Income Tax Records- 3/3 Expenses: Florists, Taxes, Telegrams, Clothing, Entertainment, and Club Dues and Donations, 1957 (Box-folder 4/16)
  - District 751 Aero Mechanic Vol 64, Vol 66, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 4/16)
  - District 751 Aero Mechanic Vol 63, Vol 65, Vol 67, 2008-2012 (Box-folder 4/18)
  - Apollo 11 Souvenir Book, "Footprints on the Moon", 1969 (Box-folder 4/19)
  - American Labor Magazine, 1969 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - A Tribute from the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers AFL-CIO: Retirement Ceremony for P.L. (Roy) Siemiller and Matthew DeMore, 1969 (Box-folder 4/21)
  - Baseball Team Correspondence, Telegram to Sen. Mon C. Wallgren, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 4/22)
  - Seattle Civilian War Commission, Correspondence (Military Service, Warren Magnuson) Union Campaign Materials, Meeting Minutes, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 4/23)
  - Papers Re: House Un-American Activities Committee, Correspondence with General Secretary Treasurer Eric Peterson, IAM Executive Council Meeting Minutes, District Council Delegates, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 4/24)
  - Correspondence with IAM President, Vice President and Secretary Treasurer, 1954 (Box-folder 4/25)
  - Personal Papers Including Correspondence, Daily Schedule, Speech Drafts, 1943 (Box-folder 4/26)
  - Pamphlet Supporting Subscription Television, 1955 (Box-folder 4/27)
  - Personal Papers- Correspondence re: War Related Issues, Congratulatory Correspondence for Election to Presidency, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 4/28)
  - Correspondence with H.W. Brown, IAM President, 1934-1941 (Box-folder 4/29)
  - Correspondence, Lists of Local Lodge Officers, District Council Delegates, District Committees, 1950-1955 (Box-folder 4/30)
  - History of District Lodge 751, Chapter 7, 1948 (Box-folder 4/31)
  - Personal Papers: Blueprint, Lease Information, Contacts, Correspondence, 1942-1947 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Political and Public Involvement: 'How to Spot a Communist' Flier, Labor in Israel, 1947 AI Lodge 751-F Election, VP Campaign Fliers, 1951, 1953 Collective Bargaining Agreements, 'Liberty: Magazine for Religious Freedom', Radio Address Supporting Prop C (1950), Labor Roundtable Radio Script (1941), Newspaper Clippings, 1941-1957 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - War Time Papers: Civilian War Commission Dissolution, Currency Exchange Control Book, Postcard from France (1944), Transcript- Gibson/Casttigan re: Wages at Boeing following War Board Decision (esp. re: women's wages), 1944-1945 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - "Hoat's Papers and Receipts, etc."- Insurance 1941, Baseball Team, US Civil Service Utilities Engineering Institute, Auto Repair and Licensing, Correspondence, 1938-1941 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Public Relations- Induction into Army, Interview as Business Agent for Lodge 751, Correspondence (Sen. Magnuson, Rep. Coffee, War Chest), 1942-1944 (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Newspaper Clippings and "Union Scrapbook," Rock Mosaic IAM Emblem, 'Our American Government', 1943-1957 (Box-folder 5/6)
  - World War II Service- National War Labor Board, Letters of Recommendation, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 5/7)
  - Event Invitations and Programs, 1931-1958 (Box-folder 5/8)
  - World War II Newspaper Clippings- National War Labor Board, Boeing Navy 'E' Award, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Bank Loans, Pay Stubs, Tax Information, Receipts, 'Training in the Aircraft Industry', Transcript of Minutes IAM Conference, 1954-1958 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Personal Papers- Car Insurance, Receipts, Correspondence (Rep. John O'Brien), 1945 (Box-folder 5/11)
  - Personal Papers- Insurance Papers, Personal Correspondence, Dept. of Public Lands- Mineral Lease, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 5/12)
  - Correspondence Re: Organizing Campaigns (Detroit, Georgia), Contract Negotiations, Negotiations in Wichita, KS, 1952 (Box-folder 5/13)
  - Personal Calendar, 1943 (Box-folder 5/14)
  - Election Rules, Personal Correspondence -Union Organizers, 1954 (Box-folder 5/15)
  - Records of Entrances/Exits by Business Representatives, Christmas Mailing List and Addresses, 1956 (Box-folder 5/16)
  - District Lodge 751 Expense Vouchers, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 5/17)
  - Lodge Election Data, Results, and Newspaper Clippings, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 5/18)
  - 1955 Lodge 751 Election- Kirkpatrick and Knight Dispute- Correspondence with Hayes (Box-folder 5/19)
  - Correspondence from Harvey W. Brown, International President, Newspaper Clippings 1942, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 5/20)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 5/21)
  - General Vice President Election- Endorsements Opponents' Posters, Correspondence, 1956 (Box-folder 5/22)
  - Officers' Vacation Schedule, 1954 (Box-folder 5/23)
  - Elections- December 1952 and January 1953 (Box-folder 5/24)
  - General Vice President Election- Endorsements, 1956 (Box-folder 5/25-26)
  - Proceedings of 21st Convention of International Association of Machinists- New York City-Leo Frison, 1945 (Box-folder 5/27)
  - Vice President's Weekly Report, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Vice President's Weekly Report, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 6/2)
  - New Machinists Building, 1960 Convention Postcards, Financial Papers and Shareholder Information- Montecopter, Inc. and Sea-Elk Corp., 1940-1998 (Box-folder 6/3)
  - Survey of Fringe Benefits Airframe Industry', 'The Economic Outlook of the Aircraft Industry', 'Administration Manual- Insurance Benefits Plan', Business Cards, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 6/4)
  - Newspaper Clippings- Contract Negotiations, Western States Conference of Machinists 1954, Salt Lake City, UT, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 6/5)
  - The Truth About the Taft-Hartley Law and its Consequences to the Labor Movement', Brief in Support of General Wage Increase for Boeing Employees, IAM Convention Roll Call 1956, San Francisco, CA, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 6/6)
  - Correspondence- Office Employees International Union Local #8, 1954 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Harold Gibson Speeches, 1950-1956 (Box-folder 6/8)
  - Correspondence- President's Office, Wage Negotiations, etc., 1951 (Box-folder 6/9)
  - Correspondence with President's Office, 1956 (Box-folder 6/10)
  - Newspaper Clippings from 1965 Strike, Aero Mechanic 1951, 1957, 1951-1965 (Box-folder 6/11)
  - Land Complaint, Newspaper Clippings, CBS Democratic Convention Report, Franco Allied Goodwill Committee, Telegram from Jackson Re: Federal Government Job, Kennedy Inauguration Invitation, Programs- Jefferson Jackson Day, Western Conference of Machinists, 1943-1976 (Box-folder 6/12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Family Pictures, Letters, Announcements, 1910s-1960s (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Proceedings -IAM Convention, San Francisco (1956), Pamphlets, Wage Data (Box-folder 7/2-3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1951-1942 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Tom Tippet's History of Lodge 751- With brief history of project in front (Box-folder 7/5)
  - Tourist Fliers, Mementos, Resolutions and Proposed Amendments from 1972 18th IAM Convention (Originally in corresponding bag in Box 19) (Box-folder 7/6)
  - John L. O'Brien Tribute Dinner Pamphlet, 1993 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - International Association of Machinists 75th Anniversary Program, 1963 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - 1956 Democratic Convention, Service Award Dinner (Hayes, Walker), IAM 75th Anniversary, Roster of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Western States Conference of Machinists, 1956-1983 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - Financial Officer Manual, Voting Information/Fliers, Pension/SS Info, 'Structure, Organization and Services of the IAM', 1947-1950 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - Collective Bargaining Educational Information, Public Notices, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 7/11)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1989 Strike, 1989 (Box-folder 7/12-13)
  - Copies of Portrait Photos - Unnamed Subject, undated (Box-folder 7/14)
  - IAM Staff Conference Winpisinger Speech, 751 Industry Report, Harriman Campaign Folder, Newspaper Clippings, Democratic National Convention 1956 Delegate Card, 1943-1963 (Box-folder 7/15)